# **BRYAN FULLER**

Vallejo, CA 94590 (210) 667-7793 - bryanfullertx@gmail.com

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An excellent record of customer and internal support paired with in depth knowledge and technical skills. Possessing a diverse skill set and solid knowledge of computer networking forged in a fast-paced high stress environment. Over 15 years customer service experience ranging from hands on high level technical IT support to retail support and customer education.

# **SKILLS**

- Very efficient at reading the customers wants and applying them to the task at hand.
- Came from a background of fanatical customer service jobs, that required going above and beyond normal job description at times.
- Have a very keen sense of a customer's concerns and can address it politely and in a timely manner.
- Excellent at communicating with coworkers and management of customers'needs and company improvements.
- Have been on call 24x7 for over 15 years in the IT industry and know how to properly handle delicate and timely situations.
- Comfortable, and knowledgeable on several operating systems (Windows, iOS, UNIX).
- Extensive data networking knowledge in Cisco within government environments, as well as Fortune 500.
- Can find information quickly and to learn new skills swiftly.

- Have the skill of being able to find an answer to anything. I can research all avenues to find a solution.
- Have dealt with million-dollar network installations, inventory management of millions of dollars' worth of Cisco equipment.
- Can quickly assess on an organizational chart who are the important people to notify.
- Can very easily explain situations to people in simple terms and can take all the time it needs for them to understand.
- Have been in many positions where I was the lead engineer on projects and neededto relay precise information at very fast intervals.
- Can assess a situation veryquickly be it IT or non-IT related.
- Have written many guidelines and procedural manuals for corporate certifications such as SAS70

# **WORK HISTORY**

# 07/2020 to 12/2020 CFO Assistant, IT Technician, Logistics Coordinator

105th Management – Oakland, CA

- CFO Assistant Helped CFO with AP/AR payments and QuickBooks entries. Filed all paper bills, receipts, and invoices creating the filing system. Responsible for mailing and shipping any packages or bills. Responsible for making sure journal entries in OuickBooks were accurate and correct.
- IT Technician Worked with contractor to help secure network and CCTV monitoring system. Helped maintain secure connections with remote location with CCTV monitoring. Configured, monitored and maintained the companies UniFi network system. Configured and installed IP phones through the campus.
- Logistics Coordinator Responsible for tracking product and maintaining inventory in vault location. Controlled the shipping to and from the facility with company product. Maintained and filed all records involving shipping to and from the facility.

### 01/2017 to Current **Driver**

# Lyft – Bay Area, CA

- Achieved consistent safety targets by adjusting driving to different road and traffic conditions and avoiding dangerous driving actions.
- Provided over 4,000 safe and timely rides to bay area passengers all while having a 4.9 rating.

### 01/2012 to 12/2017 **Owner**

# FS Consulting – Rodeo, CA

- Provided expertise with credit card terminals and register terminals used for sales transactions, including troubleshooting of receipt printers.
- Installed hard drives in security DVR's and mounted additional cameras over cash stations to achieve heightened security. Migrated DVR's, cameras, and monitoring equipment from first floor to second floor.
- Consulted with customers to assess needs and propose optimal network and security solutions.

# 03/2016 to 07/2017 Clerk/Receptionist/IT Specialist

# **Telegraph Health Center** – Oakland, CA

- Delivered expert clerical support by efficiently handling wide range of routine and special requirements (Reception, Retail Clerk, IT/Network Admin, and Security.
- Verified cards, gave change and collected and processed over \$6000 worth of cash and card payments.
- Educated customers on promotions to enhance sales.
- Increased sales 15% by offering advice on purchases and promoting additional products.

### 01/2016 to 08/2016 **Operations Manager**

# Evoxe Labs – Lafayette, CA

- Implemented policies and standard operating procedures for continuous improvement.
- Protected company assets from loss such as theft or damage by setting and enforcing effective security policies.
- Developed and implemented daily operations plans such as delivery routes, employee assignments and promotional strategies.
- Evaluated upcoming program plans to forecast expected resource needs.
- Cultivated strong business relationships with clients to increase overall experience, satisfaction and retention rates.

# 01/2013 to 05/2015 **Operations Manager**

# Steep Hill Labs – Berkeley, CA

- Multiple Roles while working here Operations Manager, Bookkeeper, Controller, AP Manager, AR Manager, Desktop IT Support Specialist, Project Manager.
- Implemented policies and standard operating procedures for continuous improvement.
- Supported operations by communicating with customers, filing documents and managing
- Acting HR and payroll processor completing bi-weekly payroll for company employees, including calculating taxes, vacation and sick time.
- Installed DropCam wifi monitoring cameras, installed printers, troubleshot desktop issues and fixed DNS and routing issues. Relocated and installed company infrastructure servers and network area storage arrays.
- Managed the physical office and lab equipment move from Oakland to Berkeley. Coordinated with multiple construction companies and moving companies.

# 01/2011 to 01/2015 Founder/Owner/Delivery Manager

# Mobile Compassionate Care Collective – Bay Area, CA

- Maintained a steady clientele of at least 50 patients, in the Contra Costa County area including Walnut Creek, Pleasant Hill, Concord, Martinez, and Clayton.
- Answered calls, took orders from customers, answered strain and dosage questions, verified patients and delivered orders in a timely manner while performing at a very high professional discretion.

## 04/2010 to 09/2012 Chief Network Engineer

### Site B Data Services LLC – San Antonio, TX

- Installed, configured, maintained Cisco 6500 edge and core routers on site and remotely.
- Built data center from the ground up installing routers, switches, phones, email/data servers, and security monitoring systems for the building including door entry systems.
- Configured, managed and evaluated multi-protocol network elements to ensure effective end-to-end communications.
- Managed application patches, data backup, security changes and network configuration and replaced boards, changed servers and loaded and tested software applications.
- Implemented WAN and LAN designs in multi-datacenter configurations.
- Installed, supported and maintained company hardware and software infrastructure according to best practices.
- Provided complete end-to-end engineering and installation of route-based IP network solutions.

- Diagnosed network problems involving combination of hardware, software, power and communications issues.
- The lead technician in delivering a 24/7 uptime guarantee as comprehensive as any in the industry.

# 

# Rackspace – San Antonio, TX

- Deployed Cisco switches, routers, and firewalls in a quick and timely manner achieving an 99.9% uptime while providing 24/7 support.
- Configured redundancy throughout the Network using protocols such as OSPF, HSRP, and BGP.
- Assisted and coordinated with Datacenter and support personnel to carry out deployments.
- Multitask numerous projects under time constraint and high-level stress.
- Provide the company with immediate informed responses for outages or network related issues.
- Process and troubleshoot Routing, DNS, IP and traffic flow tickets requiring traffic trending.
- Tested available upgrades and Network redundancy and stability.
- Quickly work through the OSI model and pinpoint issues for resolution.
- Created Visio diagrams of network infrastructure for department knowledge retention, and for training purposes.
- Trained new Network Engineers on the day-to-day operations, and configured BGP, OSPF, and Access-Lists.
- Server cabinet build out in Datacenter areas and terminated CAT-5 cable and fiber-optics to server cabinets.

# 01/2001 to 06/2003 AFCERT NetRanger Analyst

# MacAulay-Brown Inc. – San Antonio, TX

- Analyzed and dynamically shunned traffic in and out of Southwest Asia, including subnet blocking, excluding, reporting, and maintaining the CSIDS Software.
- Configured UNIX workstations including upkeep of sensors.
- Detect, document and report vulnerabilities.
- Responsible for communications with Gunter AFB and blocking traffic on AFIN routers per threats.
- Analyze network traffic on over 300 AFIN Router and Firewall sensors improving network efficiency, including analysis of traffic on known hacker ports.

# 01/1997 to 01/2001 Unix System Administrator

# United States Air Force - San Antonio, TX

- Administered and configured Solaris 2.6 servers for sensitive information message transfer.
- Configured and maintained redundant UNIX Highly Classified based critical message handling systems on a day-to-day basis.
- Provided 24-7 specialized administrative software and system support for over 2,000 local UNIX users 35,000 world-wide users.
- Coordinated procedures for remote dial-in support to the UNIX networks.
- Create and implemented UNIX scripts to run daily, weekly, and monthly back-ups on 30

# GB tape drives.

EDUCATION _	
2012-2015	Associate of Science: Computer Science and Horticulture Diablo Valley College - Pleasant Hill, CA GPA: 3.2
04/2011	Basic 101 Class: Horticulture Oaksterdam University - Oakland, CA
05/1997	USAF CCAF Communications Computer Systems Administration: Communications Computer Systems Administration 333rd Training Squadron - Keesler AFB, Biloxi, MS
05/1996	Standard High School Diploma Samuel Clemens High School - Schertz, TX

# **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

1997-2004 Maintained Top Secret/SCI TK security clearance